http://www.woodardcurran.com/privacy-statement

About
Our StoryMission & ValuesLocationsFoundationSafetyManagementPress RoomBoard of Directors
Expertise
Services
Water
Water Supply & TreatmentMunicipal WastewaterIndustrial WastewaterWater ReuseStormwaterSCADAManagement & Financial Strategies
Civil Engineering
Municipal EngineeringUrban RevitalizationOpen Space & Recreation
Operations & ManagementEnvironment
Risk AssessmentRemediationComplianceEnvironmental Planning & PermittingEcological ServicesBrownfields
Markets
GovernmentIndustrialEnergy UtilitiesInstitutionalOil & GasMining
Insights
BlogPapers & ReportsPresentationsEvents
PeopleProjectsPurpose
2016-17 CSR ReportOur Sustainability PolicyOur PeopleOur WorkOur Business OperationsOur Communities
Careers
Open PositionsCultureProfessional DevelopmentBenefitsInternships & Co-OpsRecruiting Events
About
Our StoryMission & ValuesLocationsFoundationSafetyManagementPress RoomBoard of Directors
Expertise
Services
Water
Water Supply & TreatmentMunicipal WastewaterIndustrial WastewaterWater ReuseStormwaterSCADAManagement & Financial Strategies
Civil Engineering
Municipal EngineeringUrban RevitalizationOpen Space & Recreation
Operations & ManagementEnvironment
Risk AssessmentRemediationComplianceEnvironmental Planning & PermittingEcological ServicesBrownfields
Markets
GovernmentIndustrialEnergy UtilitiesInstitutionalOil & GasMining
Insights
BlogPapers & ReportsPresentationsEvents
PeopleProjectsPurpose
2016-17 CSR ReportOur Sustainability PolicyOur PeopleOur WorkOur Business OperationsOur Communities
Careers
Open PositionsCultureProfessional DevelopmentBenefitsInternships & Co-OpsRecruiting Events
Contact
Our Commitment to Personal Information Privacy
Woodard & Curran respects your privacy, and this statement describes the data we collect through this website and how that data is stored and used. It is based on the belief that your information should be used appropriately and not shared in ways you don’t intend or expect.
Your submission of personal information on this website constitutes acknowledgment of receipt of this statement.
Information we collect
We collect information that you voluntarily provide or consent to the collection of. This includes the contact information provided when you submit our contact form, download content, or sign up to receive emails from our insights pages. Other information is collected through the use of cookies for analytics purpose so we can understand how users engage with our website. This may include your IP address and the type of browser and operating system you are using.
How we use and share your information
We may use the information you provide us to contact you in connection with your submission, specifically when you submit a question or comment to us via our contact form.
When you provide information for the purposes of downloading our insights content or via our subscribe form, we may send you content we believe may be relevant to you. You can unsubscribe from these notices via the unsubscribe links in any emails you receive.
We do not share your information with anyone outside our organization except what is collected via Google Analytics. The terms of service for Google Analytics can be found here, and further information on Google’s privacy policies can be found here. We do not otherwise disclose your information except as required by law or court order.
Retention
Information collected through this website will be retained for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this statement, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.
Links to other websites and third parties
To allow you to interact with other websites on which you may have accounts (such as LinkedIn and other social media platforms) or to apply for a job at Woodard & Curran, we may provide links or embed third-party applications that provide these connections. We are not responsible for the collection of personal information or the security or privacy of information on any third-party websites or applications. Your use of these links is subject to those platforms’ privacy policies, and you should become familiar with their practices before using the links or applications. We cannot guarantee the privacy and safety of these websites and are therefore not responsible for any content you post. Use these features at your own risk.
Use of Cookies and Related Technologies
The first time that you visit our website, we notify you about our use of cookies through a pop-up banner and we request your explicit permission. If you do not wish to accept cookies, you can adjust your web browser’s settings to restrict or eliminate them. Instructions for doing this are widely available online. Here is one such resource.
A cookie is a small data file that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive in order to identify your computer. Cookies can allow our website to identify your specific computer and browser, letting us personalize your experience. Cookies also allow us to gather anonymous statistics how you interact with our website. Specifically, we use Google Analytics as noted above. Google provides information on how this data is used at https://policies.google.com/privacy. Further information about Google uses this data can be found at https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites.
When we embed video content from websites such as YouTube or Vimeo on our website pages, these third-party websites may set a cookie when you are also logged in to their service. We do not control the dissemination of these cookies. For information about the data use and policies of these services, you will need to check their websites.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser’s settings to disable cookies if you wish. Disabling them could diminish the functionality of our website and negatively impact your experience.
Security
We take reasonable measures to protect the security of personal information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure. This includes policies that limit access, technical controls including firewalls, and other measures.
Children’s privacy
This website is intended to be used by adults and corporate entities interested in our services. We do not knowingly collect or store personal information from anyone under the age of 16. If at any time we are informed that a visitor under the age of 16 has submitted information to us through this website, we will endeavor to immediately delete the information.
Your California privacy rights
We do not provide your personal information to third parties for their use in marketing, but under California law, California residents have the right to opt-out of such use of their personal information if it occurred.
Changes to this statement
Due to changes in technology or legal requirements, we may revise this Privacy Statement from time to time.  We will notify you of changes by posting those changes on this page, or by other appropriate means.
Contact Us
What's your question about?*
People
Projects
Services
Career Opportunities
Submit
This site uses cookies to ensure you have the best experience and to analyze our traffic. Read more in our Privacy Statement.
